http://www.noveltylights.com/privacy-policy

Shopping cart
(0)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Register
Log in
Wishlist
(0)
Chasing Christmas Lights
Mini Lights for Crafts (Non-Connectable)
back
C9 LED Bulbs (Steady Burn)
Smooth Ceramic LED C7 Plastic Bulbs
C7 LED Bulbs (Steady Burn)
C7 LED Bulbs
S14 Bulbs - Medium Base (e26)
S14 LED Bulbs - Medium Base (e26)
Chasing Christmas Lights
Mini Lights for Crafts (Non-Connectable)
back
C9 LED Bulbs (Steady Burn)
Smooth Ceramic LED C7 Plastic Bulbs
C7 LED Bulbs (Steady Burn)
C7 LED Bulbs
S14 Bulbs - Medium Base (e26)
S14 LED Bulbs - Medium Base (e26)
Privacy policy
We respect your privacy!
Any and all the information collected on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned!Any information you provide will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. If you have any questions, please feel free to call or e-mail us.
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Novelty Lights Inc. uses and protects any information that you give Novelty Lights Inc when you use this website. Novelty Lights Inc is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Novelty Lights Inc. may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from Sept 1 2010.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
• contact information including email address
• demographic information such as address, zipcode
• other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
• Internal record keeping.
• We may use the information to improve our products and services.
• We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
• From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us with advertising, and how we analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. Some third-party vendors, like Google, may use these cookies to advertise on our behalf based on your past visit to our website. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies, by visiting Google's Ads Settings. You can opt out of DoubleClick's use of cookies by visiting DoubleClick Opt-out page.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
• whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
• if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at customerservice@noveltylights.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to [address]. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Contact
Novelty Lights
Phone: 1-800-209-6122
CustomerService@noveltylights.com
Mon - Fri 8am to 5pm MST
9800 E Easter Ave Suite 160 Centennial, CO 80112
Welcome to our store
Christmas Lights
Rope Lights | String Lights & More
At Novelty Lights, Inc., we pride ourselves in being the Christmas light and Outdoor String light experts with a sales staff that has years of experience with all types of Christmas and outdoor lighting projects We’ve got it all from the classic incandescent Christmas lights and the newer LED Christmas lights.
Social
Newsletter
Wait...
Copyright © 2020 Novelty Lights, Inc.. All rights reserved.
XML Site Map
